[
 {
 	"front" : "What is the largest human conflict in history?",
 	"back" : "Second World War"
 },
{
 	"front" : "The survived Nazis following the War were put on trial for crimes against humanity in which German city in 1946?",
 	"back" : "Nuremburg"
 },
 {
 	"front" : "What year did the Civil War offically start after the battle of Fort Sumter??",
 	"back" : "eighteen sixty one"
 },
 {
 	"front" : "From which kind of government was Hawaii liberated from by the United States?",
 	"back" : "Monarchy"
 },
 {
 	"front" : "What is the name of the failed invasion of Cuba ?",
 	"back" : "Bay of Pigs"
 },
 {
 	"front" : "How many presidents were also vice presidents before their terms starting after WW2?",
 	"back" : "four"
 },
 {
 	"front" : "How many presidents have been shot?",
 	"back" : "five"
 },
 {
 	"front" : "What is the worst thing about the American Elecorate system?",
 	"back" : "The Electoral College"
 },
 {
 	"front" : "Who is the largest manufacturer of weapons in the world?",
 	"back" : "The United States"
 },
 {
 	"front" : "What is the largest human conflict in history?",
 	"back" : "Second World War"
 }


]